erikalust.com 2019-04-01

# Privacy Policy - ErikaLust

This privacy policy has been created to help those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally Identifiable Information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website. We recently updated our Privacy Policy to clarify how we protect your personal information in keeping with the EU’s new General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).

We promise to keep your data safe and secure.

In brief, here is an explanation of why we need it and how we use it.

  1. **Your happiness is our No.1 Priority**

We use your data to create the best experience you can have online while you are shopping with us – and in the emails you receive from us.

  1. **We take your data seriously**

We’ll protect your data by using the services of expert data security suppliers.

  1. **We won’t spam you**

You decide what and how you hear from us by setting your preferences. You can opt-out any time you want. And with specific tags, we make sure you are not receiving emails from several automations at the same time, but only information most relevant to your needs and preferences.

  1. **We will not keep your data for the sake of it**

If we don’t need it, we will delete it.

**We take your privacy seriously**

At Lust Productions SL, we care greatly about our customers. We understand your data is precious and needs to be treated with the utmost respect and privacy. In this page, we are going to walk you through why and how we collect private data, how we use it, and your rights.

What will you find on this page?

  * How we use your information
  * Sharing your information
  * Marketing messages
  * Keeping your information
  * Your rights
  * Changes to how we protect your privacy
  * How to contact us

We use your information in a number of different ways — what we do depends on the information. The tables below set this out in detail, showing what we do, and why we do it.

### **_1 – What we collect when you browse our website_**

**Information about your phone or laptop, and how you use our website**

Information you give us when you browse our site, including your IP address and device type and, if you choose to share it with us, your location data, as well as how you use our website. We collect this via cookies, but we do not have access to your name and personal details via this technology.

**How we use information about your phone or laptop, and how you use our website and app** | **Why?**  
---|---  
Improve our website and set default options for you (such as language and currency) | To give you the best possible shopping experience  
Protect our website | To prevent and detect attacks and hackers  against either you or Lust Production SL  
  
### **_2 – What we collect when you sign up to our mailing list_**

**Your name and contact details**

**How we use your name & contact details (email)** | **Why?**  
---|---  
To send you emails and personalize it for you. | To send you emails after you’ve signed up to our mailing list, we really need your email!

And if you have given us your name, we like to send emails that do not feel anonymous!  
  
**Your history with our mailing list**

Where and when you have signed-up, in which language, what email campaigns we have sent you, which ones you have opened, which ones you have clicked through, and where you are located when you open emails.

Provide relevant content | When we see you interact more with one specific type of content, we can adjust what we send out to provide you with what you’re interested in. And by knowing in what part of the world you are located, we can send you information about events we do, stores we’re in near you, etc…  
---|---  
Adjust email frequency | To make sure we don’t spam you, we monitor your engagement with our emails and based on that, adjust what campaign you receive.  
  
You don’t have to give us any of this personal information but if you don’t, you may not be able to buy from the site, and you are unlikely to receive our optimal overall customer experience. But that is your choice – and we respect that.

We also anonymize and aggregate personal information (so that it does not identify you) and use it for purposes including testing our IT systems, research, data analysis, improving our site, and developing new products and services. We also share this information with third parties.

**What we DON’T DO:**

We do not, and will not, sell _any_ of your personal data to _any_ third party – including your name, address, email address or credit card information.

**What we DO:**

However, we share your data with the following categories of companies as an essential part of being able to provide our services to you, as set out in this statement:

  * Companies that do things to get your purchases to you, such as payment service or IT companies
  * Professional service providers, such as marketing agencies, advertising partners and website hosts, who help us run our business
  * Credit reference agencies, law enforcement and fraud prevention agencies, so we can help tackle fraud.

We may provide third parties with aggregated but anonymized information and analytics about our customers and, before we do so, we will make sure that it does not identify you.

If you signed-up to our mailing list, we will send you marketing messages by email.

**How to stop marketing messages**

You can stop receiving marketing messages from us at any time.

You can do this:

  * By clicking on the ‘unsubscribe’ link in any email
  * By contacting support@erikalust.desk-mail.com

Once you do this, we will update your profile to ensure that you don’t receive further marketing messages.

Please note that it might take a few days for all our systems to be updated, so you might get messages from us while we process your request.

Please note as well that stopping marketing messages will not stop service communications (such as order updates or customer care follow-up if you have contacted us).

We’ll hold on to your information for as long as you have your account, or as long as is needed to be able to provide the services to you, or (in the case of any contact you may have with our Customer Care team) for as long as is necessary to provide support-related reporting and trend analysis only.

If reasonably necessary or required to meet legal or regulatory requirements, resolve disputes, prevent fraud and abuse, or enforce our terms and conditions, we may also keep hold of some of your information as required, even after you have closed your account or it is no longer needed to provide the services to you.

When it comes to your personal information, here are your rights:

  * The right to be informed about how your personal information is being used.
  * The right to access the personal information we hold about you. You can contact us at support@erikalust.desk-mail.com.
  * The right to request the correction of inaccurate personal information we hold about you. Simply contact us at support@erikalust.desk-mail.com
  * The right to request that we delete your data, or stop processing it or collecting it, in some circumstances. Again, we’re available at contact us at support@erikalust.desk-mail.com.
  * The right to stop direct marketing messages, by unsubscribing. Ask us at support@erikalust.desk-mail.com.
  * The right to request that we transfer or port elements of your data either to you or another service provider. Ask us at support@erikalust.desk-mail.com.

If you want to exercise your rights, or just have questions, please contact us at support@erikalust.desk-mail.com.

We may change this page from time to time, to reflect how we are processing your data.

If we make significant changes, we will make that clear on the website, or by some other means of contact such as email, so that you are able to review the changes before.

If you have any questions regarding your data, please contact us contact us at support@erikalust.desk-mail.com.

And also if you have any questions about our products, an order with us or any ticket you’ve created with us, contact us at support@erikalust.desk-mail.com.
